Office of the President Records UA001
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Jean Mayer, administrative records and related papers, 1939 -- 2006; 1976 -- 1992; UA001.013; 45.6 Linear Feet; 2 Digital Object(s)
  - [Mayer at Jumbo stampede with Mark Crimmis], 1979; UA001.013.036.00073 (Box 36)
  - [Board of Overseers, School of Veterninary Medicine], 1979; UA001.013.036.00074 (Box 36)
  - [Mayer with wife at Millennium dinner], 1985; UA001.013.036.00075 (Box 36)
  - [Mayer's lecture at 3rd seminar on pharmaceutical public policy issues], 1975; UA001.013.036.00076 (Box 36)
  - [Photos], 1975; UA001.013.036.00077 (Box 36)
  - [Mayer with mayor and city council], 1975; UA001.013.036.00078 (Box 36)
  - [Photos taken from album], 1980; UA001.013.036.00079 (Box 36)
    Photos were taken from a Fujicolor album.
  - [Mayer at Radcliffe Centennial], 1978; UA001.013.036.00080 (Box 36)
  - [Mayer with family of Tae H. Yop], 1982; UA001.013.036.00081 (Box 36)
  - [Mayer travel photos], UA001.013.036.00082 (Box 36)
  - [Photos], UA001.013.036.00083 (Box 36)
  - [Mayer with Mr. and Mrs. Harry Day and Mrs. Sam Weisberg], 1979; UA001.013.036.00084 (Box 36)
  - [Photos], UA001.013.036.00085 (Box 36)
  - [Photo of Dr. Jose Ferrandiz, Gino Passamont, Dr. Philip Williams, Dr. Dario Castellini and Kristen Downes], 1990; UA001.013.036.00086 (Box 36)
  - [Photo of Dr. Ed Carney, Bob Meserve and Dr. Ed Becker], 1990; UA001.013.036.00087 (Box 36)
  - [Mayer cutting tape of Becker alumni room with Dean Erling Johansen and Ed Becker and Allen Callow], 1990; UA001.013.036.00088 (Box 36)
  - [Photos], UA001.013.036.00089 (Box 36)
  - [Mayer presenting at the Industrial College of the Armed Forces with Graham Parsons, Colonel W.R. McKelvey and Lt. General John S. Hardy.], 1969; UA001.013.036.00090 (Box 36)
  - [Photos], UA001.013.036.00091 (Box 36)
  - [Mounted photos from display], 1992; UA001.013.036.00092 (Box 36)
  - [Mounted photos from display], 1992; UA001.013.036.00093 (Box 36)
  - [Mounted photos from display], 1992; UA001.013.036.00094 (Box 36)
  - [Bachrach brochure], 1975; UA001.013.036.00095 (Box 36)
  - [President's Ball], 1977; UA001.013.036.00096 (Box 36)
  - [Mayer recieves award in Bangkok], 1984; UA001.013.036.00097 (Box 36)
  - [Mayer mounted photo], 1984; UA001.013.036.00098 (Box 36)
  - [Photos], UA001.013.036.00099 (Box 36)
  - Order of St. Lazarus of Jerusalem, 1976; UA001.013.037.00001 (Box 37)
  - The Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy mounted photo, 1976; UA001.013.037.00002 (Box 37)
  - Ballou Hall mounted photo, 1976; UA001.013.037.00003 (Box 37)
  - Lewis Hall mounted photo, 1976; UA001.013.037.00004 (Box 37)
  - Women's Lacrosse team mounted photo, 1976; UA001.013.037.00005 (Box 37)
  - Goddard Chapel mounted photo, 1976; UA001.013.037.00006 (Box 37)
  - President Jean Mayer mounted photo, 1980; UA001.013.037.00007 (Box 37)
  - Biology laboratory mounted photo, 1980; UA001.013.037.00008 (Box 37)
  - Wessell Library mounted photo, 1980; UA001.013.037.00009 (Box 37)
  - Fine Arts Studio mounted photo, 1980; UA001.013.037.00010 (Box 37)
  - Dr. Seymour O. Sinclos mounted photo, 1980; UA001.013.037.00011 (Box 37)
  - Mayer Portrait Proofs mounted photo, 1970; UA001.013.038.00001 (Box 38)
  - Friends of Dr. Mayer WW II Resistance Group, 1970; UA001.013.038.00002 (Box 38)
  - [Chicago Medical School Honorary Degree], 1991; UA001.013.038.00003 (Box 38)
  - [Western New England College Honorary Degree], 1977; UA001.013.038.00004 (Box 38)
  - [Yale University Award], 1977; UA001.013.038.00005 (Box 38)
  - Jean Mayer, 1975; UA001.013.DO.00104; Unknown (Box Shared 84)
    Portraits; People; College presidents; Office of the President, Jean Mayer, records; Mayer, Jean; Office of the President
  - Elizabeth Van Huysen Mayer and daughter, 1980; UA001.013.DO.00105; Unknown (Box Shared 84)
    People; Events; Office of the President, Jean Mayer, records; Mayer, Elizabeth Van Huysen
- John DiBiaggio, administrative records and related papers, 1976 -- 2005; 1990 -- 2001; UA001.014; 49.2 Linear Feet; 1 Artifact(s); 1 Digital Object(s)
  This series consists of correspondence, memoranda, reports and general subject files documenting the presidency of John DiBiaggio. The bulk of the material focuses on DiBiaggio's duties and activities as president. There are little or no materials on his positions held elsewhere or other aspects of his career. Dr. John DiBiaggio served as the eleventh president of Tufts University from 1992 to 2002.
  This series is organized into four subseries: Subject files; Correspondence; Speeches; and Photographs.
  - Subject files, 1976 -- 2005; 1990 -- 1996; UA001.014.001; 42.0 Linear Feet
    This subseries consists of subject files containing memoranda, correspondence, reports and related materials documenting the duties and events of John DiBiaggio's presidency at Tufts University. Also included are subject files from the Jean Mayer presidency. These files have been combined with those of DiBiaggios in an effort to maintain original order.
    - "A" general, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    - "A" general, 1992 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    - "A" general, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    - Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - Admissions, 1991 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    - Admissions, 1992 -- 1993; UA001.014.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    - Admissions, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    - Admissions, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    - Admissions, 2000; UA001.014.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    - Admissions: April open house, 1999; UA001.014.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    - Admissions: April open house, 1999 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    - Admissions: class of 2005, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    - Admissions: class of 2006, 2001; UA001.014.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    - Admissions: graduate school candidates, 2001; UA001.014.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
    - Admissions: pending, academic year 1995-1996, 1994 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    - Admissions: veterinary, 2001; UA001.014.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
    - African-American Center, 1990 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
    - Alcohol issue, 1997 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
    - Alcohol policy, 1998 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
    - Algonquin Club, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
    - Alumni, 1987 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
    - Alumni, 1992 -- 1993; UA001.014.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
    - Alumni, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
    - Alumni, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
    - Alumni, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
    - Alumni, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
    - Alumni, 1995; UA001.014.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
    - Alumni Association executives, 1995; UA001.014.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
    - Alumni relations: alliances & clubs, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
    - Alumni relations: awards, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
    - Alumni relations: general correspondence, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
    - Alumni relations: letters, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
    - Amalgamates, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
    - America Reads, 1997 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
    - American Academy of Dental Science: keynote address, The Harvard Club, April 9, 1998; UA001.014.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
    - American Association of Presidents of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1992; UA001.014.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
    - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
    - American Association of Colleges and Universities, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
    - American Association of Dental Schools, 1999 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
    - American Association for Higher Education, 1996 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1997 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
    - American Association of University Women, 1995; UA001.014.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
    - American Cancer Society, 1993 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
    - American Cancer Society Foundation, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
    - American Cancer Society Foundation: smoke free campaign, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
    - American College of Dentists: Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1995; UA001.014.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
    - American College of Dentists: Sheraton Boston, 1996; UA001.014.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
    - American Council on Education, 1984 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
    - American Council on Education: fellows, 1996 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
    - American Council on Education: general correspondence, 1994 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
    - American Council on Education: general correspondence, 1999 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
    - American Council on Education: general correspondence, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
    - American Council on Education: general correspondence, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
    - American Council on Education: plenary session, February 9, 1998; UA001.014.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
    - American Council on Education: president search, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
    - American Council on Education-CRE transatlantic dialogue, San Miniato, Italy, June 25-28, 1999; UA001.014.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
    - American Council on Education: straight talk about college costs and prices, 1998; UA001.014.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
    - American Council on Education: UNESCO, 1999; UA001.014.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
    - American Dental Association: Chicago, Illinois, July 14-15, 1995; UA001.014.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
    - American Ireland Fund, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
    - America's Promise, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
    - Animal experimentation, 1984 -- 1990; UA001.014.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
    - Animal experimentation, 1992 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
    - Archives, 1996 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
    - Armenian Chair, 1998; UA001.014.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
    - Art gallery, 1983 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
    - Art gallery, 1992 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
    - Articles, 1995 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
    - Arts and Sciences, 1984 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
    - Arts and Sciences, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
    - Arts and Sciences: faculty, 1989 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
    - Arts and Sciences: faculty meeting, President's remarks, September 2, 1998; UA001.014.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
    - Arts and Sciences: faculty meeting remarks, November 7, 1998; UA001.014.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
    - Arts and Sciences: Graduate School, 1986 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
    - Arts and Sciences: Graduate School, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
    - Arts and Sciences: Graduate School, 1991 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
    - Arts and Sciences: telecommunications park, 1997 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
    - Arts and Sciences: undergraduate, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
    - Arts and Sciences: undergraduate, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
    - Asian-American, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1991 -- 1993; UA001.014.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1991 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
    - Association of American Colleges and Universities, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
    - Association of American Colleges and Universities, 2001; UA001.014.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
    - Association of American Universities, 1991 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1992 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
    - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts, 1990 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
    - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
    - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts, 1995; UA001.014.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
    - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts, 1992 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
    - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in Massachusetts, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
    - Athletics: President Mayer, correspondence, 1983 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
    - Athletics, 1990 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
    - Athletics: Galway, 1990 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
    - Awards, 1991 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
    - Awards, 1996; UA001.014.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
    - Awards: Presidential Award for Citizenship and Public Affairs, 1999; UA001.014.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
    - Awards: Second Annual Presidential Award, 2000; UA001.014.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
    - "B" general, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
    - "B" general, 1983 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
    - "B" general, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
    - "B" general, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
    - Barnum Museum, 1989 -- 1993; UA001.014.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
    - Barron's, 1993; UA001.014.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
    - Benefits, 1998 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
    - Blueprint: a vision for Tufts tomorrow, 1996 -- 1997; UA001.014.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers: Arts and Sciences, 1997 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers: Athletics, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers: Athletics, 1997 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers: Council, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers: Dental, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers: Engineering, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers: Fletcher, 1997 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers: General, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers: International, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers: Library, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
    - Board of Overseers: Medical School, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
    - Board of Overseers: nutrition, 1997 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
    - Board of Overseers: Veterinary School, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
    - Board of Regents of Higher Education, 1988 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees, 1992 -- 1993; UA001.014.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees, 1993 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees, 1994; UA001.014.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: Academic Affairs Committee, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: Administrative and Finance Committee, n.d., UA001.014.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: biographical record of Dr. John DiBiaggio, 1996 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: Compensation Committee, 1999; UA001.014.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: Executive Committee, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: Executive Committee meeting, January 5, 1999; UA001.014.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: Executive Committee meeting, March 11, 1999; UA001.014.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: Executive Committee meeting, April 13, 1999; UA001.014.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: Executive Committee meeting, June 1, 1999; UA001.014.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: Executive Committee meeting, September 7, 1999; UA001.014.001.005.00021 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: Executive Committee meeting, March 6, 2001; UA001.014.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: general correspondence, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: general correspondence, 1998 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: Investment Committee, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: Investment Committee, 1998 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees, February 6-7, 1998; UA001.014.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees, November 6-7, 1998; UA001.014.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees, February 5-6, 1999; UA001.014.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees, November 3-4, 2000; UA001.014.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: retreat, November 7-8, 1997; UA001.014.001.005.00031 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: trustee giving, 1996; UA001.014.001.005.00032 (Box 5)
    - Board of Trustees: Trusteeship Committee, 1997 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
    - Books, 1992 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
    - Bookstore, 1999 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
    - Boston, 1983 -- 1990; UA001.014.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
    - Boston Against Drugs, 1994; UA001.014.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
    - Boston business community, 1992 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
    - Boston Committee on Foreign Relations, 1998; UA001.014.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
    - Boston Higher Education Partnership, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
    - Boston Higher Education Partnership, 1992 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
    - Boston Higher Education Partnership, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
    - Boston newspapers, 1993 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
    - Boston School of Occupational Therapy-5, 1993 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
    - Brennan Group, 2001; UA001.014.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
    - Bretton Woods Committee, 1998 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
    - Budget, 1990 -- 1991; UA001.014.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
    - Buildings and grounds, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
    - Business-Higher Education Forum, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
    - Business-Higher Education Forum, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
    - Business-Higher Education Forum, 2000 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
    - Business-Higher Education Forum: task force, 2000; UA001.014.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
    - Business process redesign, 1997 -- 1998; UA001.014.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
    - "C" general, 1990 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.006.00022 (Box 6)
    - "C" general, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.006.00023 (Box 6)
    - "C" general, 1992 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.006.00024 (Box 6)
    - "C" general, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.006.00025 (Box 6)
    - Campus Center, 1991 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.006.00026 (Box 6)
    - Campus Compact, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.006.00027 (Box 6)
    - Campus Compact, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.006.00028 (Box 6)
    - Campus Compact, 1994 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.006.00029 (Box 6)
    - Campus Compact, 1993 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.006.00030 (Box 6)
    - Campus Compact, 1996; UA001.014.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
    - Campus Compact, 1999; UA001.014.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
    - Career Services, 1997 -- 1999; UA001.014.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
    - Cassidy, 1990 -- 1993; UA001.014.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
    - Cassidy, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
    - Cassidy, 1994 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
    - Cassidy, 1998 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
    - Center for Environmental Management, 1992 -- 1993; UA001.014.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
    - Center for Environmental Management, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.007.00009 (Box 7)
    - Center for Environmental Management, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.007.00010 (Box 7)
    - Center for Environmental Management, 1993; UA001.014.001.007.00011 (Box 7)
    - Center on Hunger, Poverty and Nutrition Policy, 1992 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.007.00012 (Box 7)
    - Center on Hunger, Poverty and Nutrition Policy, 1993 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.007.00013 (Box 7)
    - Center for the Study of Drug Development, 1992 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.007.00014 (Box 7)
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency, 1996 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.007.00015 (Box 7)
    - Center for the Study of Sport in Society, 1993 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.007.00016 (Box 7)
    - Center for Studying Health System Change, 1998; UA001.014.001.007.00017 (Box 7)
    - Center for Teaching and Advising, 1993; UA001.014.001.007.00018 (Box 7)
    - Chaplaincy, 1989 -- 1992; UA001.014.001.007.00019 (Box 7)
    - Chaplaincy, 1996 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.007.00020 (Box 7)
    - Charitable Campaign, 1993; UA001.014.001.007.00021 (Box 7)
    - Charitable Campaign, 1993; UA001.014.001.007.00022 (Box 7)
    - Charitable Campaign, 1995 -- 1996; UA001.014.001.007.00023 (Box 7)
    - Charitable Campaign, 1992 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.007.00024 (Box 7)
    - Charitable Campaign, 1997 -- 2000; UA001.014.001.008.00001 (Box 8)
    - Charitable Campaign-7, 1985 -- 1987; UA001.014.001.008.00002 (Box 8)
    - Charitable Campaign, 1988 -- 1990; UA001.014.001.008.00003 (Box 8)
    - Charitable Campaign-8, 1984 -- 1988; UA001.014.001.008.00004 (Box 8)
    - Charitable Campaign, 1992; UA001.014.001.008.00005 (Box 8)
    - Charitable Campaign, 1991; UA001.014.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
    - Chronicle of Higher Education-5, 1992 -- 1995; UA001.014.001.008.00007 (Box 8)
    - College Board-8, 1994 -- 1998; UA001.014.001.008.00008 (Box 8)
    - College Board, 1999 -- 2001; UA001.014.001.008.00009 (Box 8)
    - College and University Personnel Association-4, 1992 -- 1994; UA001.014.001.008.00010 (Box 8)
    - Christopher Columbus Celebrate Discovery Award, 2000; UA001.014.001.008.00011 (Box 8)
    - Christopher Columbus Celebrate Discovery Award, 1998; UA001.014.001.008.00012 (Box 8)
    - Christopher Columbus Celebrate Discovery Award-8, 1997 -- 1998; UA001.014.001.008.00013 (Box 8)
    - Christopher Columbus Celebrate Discovery Award-7, 1990 -- 1997; UA001.014.001.008.00014 (Box 8)
    - Christopher Columbus Rediscovering Southeast Asia Symposium, 1997; UA001.014.001.008.00015 (Box 8)
    - Commencement, 1989; UA001.014.001.008.00016 (Box 8)
    - Commencement, 1990; UA001.014.001.008.00017 (Box 8)